onmybloq.in 2010-12-11

# Privacy Policy

**Personal Information Collected by OnMyBloq**  
Your privacy is very important to us and is our prime concern. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy, so you will understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose, and make use of your personal information. The following discussion outlines our privacy policy. We collect the domain name, IP and e-mail address (where possible) of visitors to our web pages along with aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, user-specific information on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations, profiles, photos and images.  

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web page, used to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor, used to notify consumers about updates to our Web site, update user profile and notification about sponsored events, services, contest and products.

Full disclosure of personal information will be provided by onmybloq to law enforcement agencies as required by law in order to protect onmybloq, affiliates and the public fully from harm.

**Inviting Friends  
**If you choose to use our site to rate or invite a friend, we will ask for your friendís name and email address. Omybloq will then send a one- time email message to your friend to inform that individual that he or she has been ìratedî or invited to join the onmybloq website. Your email address and email response will be stored to track successful referrals to the onmybloq website.

**Internet Awareness  
**Information voluntarily posted in public areas, such as weblogs, journals, message boards, forums, and chat rooms, can be viewed by the public. Please use discretion when disclosing any information to avoid unsolicited or unwanted/undesirable communications.

**Children  
**Children under the age of thirteen (13) are prohibited from becoming members and submitting any personal information to onmybloq. Any users verified to be under the age of (13) years of age, will have their profile deleted as quickly as possible. If you suspect a user is under the age of (13), please contact provided us with personal information without parental or guardian consent, the parent or guardian should contact us to remove the information at privacy@onmybloq immediately.

**Use of Cookies  
**We use cookies to store visitors preferences, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, alert visitors to new areas that we think might be of interest to them when they return to our site, record past activity at a site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site , customize Web page content based on visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends.

**Third Party Advertising  
**With respect to Ad Servers: To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages.Onmybloq may share your profile,email address to third parties in order to offer members more targeted advertising and useful products and services.

**Links  
**Onmybloq may display links to other websites. We encourage users to view the specific privacy policy of ALL websites they may visit, using one of our links. Onmybloq will not be responsible for any privacy policies other then those of Onmybloq. 

**Ownership Transfer  
**onmybloq reserves all rights to transfer all personal information and content in the event of a transfer of ownership, merger, or acquisition. Any material changes to privacy policy as a result of any acquisition or merger will be communicated to members beforehand. 

**Security  
**Onmybloq uses generally accepted industry standard technology that is designed to ensure the safety of your personal information. Protect your account and password, and do not give either to unauthorized people. If you have any other questions about the security of our website, please contact us.

**Changes in Privacy Policy  
**From time to time we may update this Privacy Policy. At that time, we will post a notice of any significant changes on our website. Keep yourself informed by visiting this site periodically to view such changes. Personally identifiable information provided to Onmybloq will be subject to the provisions of the current existing Privacy Policy.

**Deactivating Membership  
**Membership to Onmybloq can be deactivated at any time by logging on to your account and hitting the deactivation selection and following its simple instructions.

**Contact  
**If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please contact us at [privacy@onmybloq.com](mailto:privacy@onmybloq.com). You can also reach us by mail at onmybloq, 107 Carsdale Drive, Winnipeg, Manitoba, Canada, R2V 4W6.
